May you one day find true love.
That is the very wish that lives
within that ring of yours.
I should find true love?
Exactly.
And it's our job
to make sure we find it.
That's why, Lara,
you're going to set out
to the open sea from now on.
Would you like to see
a special place
that we haven't told
anybody about?
We can take you there.
When you see the moon
from the secret spot,
it looks huge.
Everyone's so happy...
because you have become
one of the princesses.
Is there somewhere
that you'd like to go to, Lara?
I guess I shouldn't say this,
but I'd really like to see
the human world.
[♪ calm music]
[♪ opening music begins]
[♪ opening music ends]
[birds chirping]
[groans softly]
[alarm] Wake up, it's 6 AM.
Time for your
early morning workout.
What?
Huh?
Lex, what is happening?
All right,
let me think about this.
Somehow I came back to life,
and I heard a voice calling me.
[gasps]
[♪ mysterious music]
Oh, I remember now.
That was the potion that turns
mermaids into humans.
The next thing I remember,
I was hit by...
that human who's terrifying!
I heard that Lady Witch
has many servants
under her control.
Was that one of them?
Does that mean she tricked me?
Lady Witch must have
captured me, and now-—
[alarm]
Time for your
early morning workout.
Time for your early mo-—
[glass shatters]
Huh?
[♪ upbeat music]
-What is this world?
-Care to explain yourself?
[yells]
[panting]
What should I do?
I have to hide somewhere.
[helicopter whirring]
Oh, that's-—
This building
is the biggest church
we have in this entire country.
It's the closest place
to God's love and protection.
[♪ upbeat music continues]
Lara, I still love you.
Oh, Father.
[door creaks]
[♪ ominous music]
[screaming]
No! Don't come any closer!
Keep away!
Um, I'm a princess
of the royal family!
[WOMAN] Lara.
That's Lady Witch's voice.
Where is it coming from?
Lara?
Hey, Lara.
I'm down here.
Huh? Why does that fish
sound like Lady Witch?
It's probably because it is me.
Hey.
Just who are you?
My bedroom window, my room...
are both a total mess.
What are you going to do
about that?
[WITCH] Lara!
You threw away
my Haddo too.
-Can you hear me?
-What if it breaks?
-Pay attention.
-Are you listening?
-What are you going to do?
-Can you hear me?
-Answer me!
-Lara!
Mari, dinner.
[thud]
Dad...
[♪ upbeat music]
Grandma, I'm staying
at a friend's tonight.
-Which friend?
-It's fine, right?
It's not fine.
Who is this friend?
-It's okay, isn't it?
-What's okay about it?
Mari, isn't your friend
going to eat?
Oh, that's right.
Mari has a friend.
This is the first time
I see one of your friends.
Did you say Mari's friend?
Mari actually made a friend.
You do know I talk
to Gon-chan as well.
You idiot.
You know fish don't talk.
-But I went to all this trouble.
-It's okay, I'll eat it.
[WITCH] So then, I see
you've accepted those legs.
My little gift to you.
Is it true?
I need to know,
are you really Lady Witch?
Yes, I am.
It's been a while, Lara.
But I don't understand.
What happened to you?
You're now a small fish!
How observant.
Also, what was everything I saw
in those mirrors?
It's all true.
Where we are is now a place
called Shiga.
The mermaids lost their castle,
so I led them all the way here.
To this wonderful land.
However, it made no difference
what I did.
Their light continued
to fade away.
The citizens, the royal family,
and Rowan...
they're all in a deep sleep
in my mansion right now.
Well, I suppose they may as well
be dead, if I'm brutally honest.
Lara, it's all your fault.
[gasps]
You shouldn't act too surprised.
They lost their light because
you broke the law.
To think this all happened
because you decided
to fall in love with some
measly human being.
It's because of me? Father...
The castle...
has lost its light.
That's right.
Although I remember
what you said,
that it's possible
I could find a way
to bring my family back to life.
[WITCH] If the light
is ever lost,
just find a way to get it back.
You must go
and find true love, Lara.
You are a princess.
[gasps]
It's dark.
Successfully connected
to Wi-Fi.
[MARI] Thank goodness...
it's still working.
You're lucky, but you've got
to pay for the window.
[WITCH] Mari,
I'm still hungry, you know.
No way, you've been gaining
too much weight.
-Hey, Haddo, order me some cake.
-Hey, Haddo, cancel that.
-Hey!
-What?
You know what happens
if I don't get my way.
-Wow, I'm so scared.
-I can't.
There's nothing
I can do about it anymore.
[WITCH] Hmph,
so you're giving up then?
You've lost your castle,
your family is gone.
And yet you are the only one
who can save them.
You know,
you're really chatty today.
[sobs]
Why are you making her cry,
Gon-chan?
All I did
was tell her the truth.
You really don't have
any tact, do you?
That's who I am.
What's wrong with that?
She feels attacked by you.
It's not my fault
she's a crybaby.
My ring!
Where is my royal ring?
[MARI] Your ring?
Did you lose it?
Whatever, forget about it.
You don't need it.
[gasps]
[WITCH] Lara,
where are you going?
Hey, Mari, chase after her!
-Why though?
-Just do it already.
Later. I've got to get
to practice soon.
[WITCH] Hey,
you have to listen to me!
Please, Mari!
She has the potential to bring
Shiga Town down!
She's a princess!
Yeah, she's a princess.
So what?
[WITCH] Hey, Mari!
I'll get it back,
whatever it takes.
Good to see you.
It has been a while
since you've been here.
-What brings you to town today?
-Nothing much.
I thought it would be nice
to see an old friend.
I'm so glad it's still working.
Lady Lisa, what's that light?
I don't know. However...
if this ring
has resonated with it...
Lara!
[dogs barking]
Shiro!
What's wrong with you, Shiro?!
Shiga, what a terrifying place
this is.
Huh?
The area where I lost
my important ring...
Just where is that place?
What are you doing there?
Are you a customer?
You don't look like one.
What's up with this girl?
What's the matter, huh?
Oh dear, I don't think
she understands.
It could be that she's lost.
Maybe we should drive her
to the station.
Oh, drive!
[horse galloping]
Should we stop at a police box
and ask?
I wonder what's up with her.
There's a scar on her tongue.
Don't be silly,
you must be seeing things.
-Where are you going?
-What's she doing?
Why is this world so weird?
I don't understand anything.
I don't know where to go.
-Huh?
-Hi there!
We're running
a special promotion
for new HopCard members
if you want to sign up.
I don't understand.
What's this?
It's simple.
If you're new and you sign up,
we're offering up to 200 points
if you decide
to get a card today.
Huh?
In order to start
your application,
please fill in your information
in the space outlined in bold.
This booklet contains all of the
HopCard terms and conditions.
Now, regarding
your accumulated Hop points...
I don't have any time
for this kind of thing.
[DOLL] Come and play with me
and my friends in the ocean.
Come and- come and- come and-
come and play with me
and my friends in the ocean.
I just don't understand it
at all.
What's the deal
with this Shiga town?
I want to go home.
Back to... the ocean.
[bird squawking]
[♪ emotional music]
Wait, isn't that...
[panting]
My ring!
It's there... somewhere!
A very special and wonderfully
radiant princess.
That is exactly
what our mother was like.
Even the very light that brings
this castle to life,
it was all created by her.
And there might be a chance
that maybe one of us princesses
has that power
that our mother once had.
Huh?
[whimpers]
There's no use staring
at your hands.
It's the light
that is born out of love.
Tell me, Lara,
have you ever felt that warm,
tingling love somewhere deep
within your heart?
Hmm, I'm not really getting it.
Well, that's okay, because it's
only when a chosen princess
feels true love
that a radiant light
begins to well up
from deep within her heart.
So then
all six of us princesses
are searching for true love
to bring that light.
After all, we have a mission,
and that mission
is to bring that light...
to everyone in this castle.
That's why we're all here.
No! I can't find it!
Why?
Could it be?
I've lost my ring.
I've lost my family.
And now...
I've lost my home.
What?
My lights!
Why can't I breathe?!
I can't move.
No!
I've even lost the sea.
I can't go back...
...anymore.
[Mari pants]
[Lara coughs]
Wow, it's you.
All right, what is your problem?
You just decided to walk into
Lake Biwa and start drowning?
You're a mermaid, but what good
is that if you can drown?
This is all your fault!
Huh?
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have lost my ring!
Huh? You're the one
who bumped into me!
That ring is important to me!
Well, the stuff in my room
is important too.
Don't forget about my window.
[MARI] Come on, let's go.
[machine beeping]
[soft thud]
[LARA] Oh!
Huh?
[♪ soft music]
[drinking sounds]
Delicious.
By the way, thank you.
-Hmm?
-For helping me.
-No biggie.
-I really am quite an idiot...
for not saying thank you.
Even if...
even if you're the servant
to Lady Witch.
[MARI] Huh? Lady Witch?
You mean Gon-chan?
I'm not her servant.
[LARA] Huh? You're not?
[MARI] If anything,
that fish is really my pet.
A lady witch is your pet?
Is that true?
Who on earth are you?
My name is Mari.
Mari Otsu.
Mari.
That's a lovely name.
[♪ gentle song]
♪ That train,
where we are coming from ♪
♪ Going to that place
we have never been ♪
Huh?
-You really just found her?
-Yeah.
Gon-chan was on the verge
of death when I first saw her.
So I made her my pet.
[LARA] Your pet?
You do know she's
a terrifying witch, right?
Well, right now she's just
a cute little fish.
[LARA] You're so weird, Mari.
Yeah, well,
you're a pretty weird mermaid.
I'm going to sleep now.
Lady Witch, are you awake?
I want to apologize.
I ran away this morning...
because I was terrified
that there would be no way
I would ever regain the Light of
Love, especially after I died.
[witch scoffs] I could
have not gotten involved at all,
you know?
Hey, Lady Witch,
do you think I'll find it?
Can I find true love right
here in Shiga?
Let's go home.
-Hey, Lady Witch...
-Go to sleep!
[♪ closing music begins]
[♪ closing music ends]
-Huh!
-Oh!
[MALE] Wow.
Lady Lisa,
you said it would be like this.
Huh?
She's special.
She's the chosen princess.
I know you will find it,
my beloved Lara.